<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homes on Yin Cui</title>
    <link>http://www.cs.cornell.edu/~ycui/home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homes on Yin Cui</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2017 Yin Cui</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.cs.cornell.edu/~ycui/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>http://www.cs.cornell.edu/~ycui/home/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.cs.cornell.edu/~ycui/home/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I am Yin Cui (崔崟 in Chinese, pronounced as /yin tsui/), a 4th-year Ph.D. candidate in the Department of Computer Science at Cornell University and Cornell Tech. I am very fortunate to be a member of SE(3) Computer Vision Group led by Professor Serge Belongie. My research interests lie in the field of Computer Vision and Machine Learning. For more information, please refer to my Curriculum Vitae.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research Highlights</title>
      <link>http://www.cs.cornell.edu/~ycui/home/publication/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.cs.cornell.edu/~ycui/home/publication/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>http://www.cs.cornell.edu/~ycui/home/lists/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.cs.cornell.edu/~ycui/home/lists/</guid>
      <description>2018  Yin Cui, Yang Song, Chen Sun, Andrew Howard, Serge Belongie. Large Scale Fine-Grained Categorization and Domain-Specific Transfer Learning. IEEE Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR) 2018.
 Grant Van Horn, Oisin Mac Aodha, Yang Song, Yin Cui, Chen Sun, Alex Shepard, Hartwig Adam, Pietro Perona, Serge Belongie. The iNaturalist Species Classification and Detection Dataset. IEEE Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR) 2018 (Spotlight). [Data]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous</title>
      <link>http://www.cs.cornell.edu/~ycui/home/misc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.cs.cornell.edu/~ycui/home/misc/</guid>
      <description>Professional Activities  Co-founder of Common Visual Data Foundation (CVDF), 2016 - Present. Organizing Committee of ImageNet and COCO Visual Recognition Workshop at ICCV&amp;rsquo;15, ECCV&amp;rsquo;16. Organizing Committee of Joint Workshop of the COCO and Places Challenges at ICCV&amp;rsquo;17. Organizing Committee of Joint COCO and Mapilary Recognition Challenge Workshop at ECCV&amp;rsquo;18. Organizing Committee of Fine-Grained Visual Categorization Workshop at CVPR&amp;rsquo;17, CVPR&amp;rsquo;18. Organizing Committee of Large-scale Scene Understanding Workshop (MS COCO Captioning Challenge) at CVPR&amp;rsquo;15.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>