<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homes on Yin Cui</title>
    <link>/home/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homes on Yin Cui</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2021 Yin Cui</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/home/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/home/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, I am Yin Cui (崔崟 in Chinese, pronounced as /yin tsui/), a Research Scientist at Google. Before joining Google, I obtained my Ph.D. in Computer Science from Cornell University and Cornell Tech in 2019, advised by Professor Serge Belongie. My research interests are Computer Vision and Machine Learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Selected Publications</title>
      <link>/home/lists/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/lists/</guid>
      <description>Full list of publications available in Google Scholar.
 Open-vocabulary Object Detection via Vision and Language Knowledge Distillation
Xiuye Gu, Tsung-Yi Lin, Weicheng Kuo, Yin Cui
arXiv:2104.13921 [arXiv]
 Revisiting 3D ResNets for Video Recognition
Xianzhi Du, Yeqing Li, Yin Cui, Rui Qian, Jing Li, Irwan Bello
arXiv:2109.01696 [arXiv] [Code]
 VATT: Transformers for Multimodal Self-Supervised Learning from Raw Video, Audio and Text
Hassan Akbari, Liangzhe Yuan, Rui Qian, Wei-Hong Chuang, Shih-Fu Chang, Yin Cui, Boqing Gong</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Miscellaneous</title>
      <link>/home/misc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/home/misc/</guid>
      <description> Professional Activities  Organizing Committee of ImageNet and COCO Visual Recognition Workshop at ICCV 2015, ECCV 2016 Organizing Committee of Joint Workshop of the COCO and Places Challenges at ICCV 2017 Organizing Committee of Joint COCO and Mapilary Recognition Challenge Workshop at ECCV 2018, ICCV 2019 Organizing Committee of Joint COCO and LVIS Recognition Challenge Workshop at ECCV 2020 Organizing Committee of Fine-Grained Visual Categorization Workshop at CVPR 2017, CVPR 2018 Organizing Committee of Large-scale Scene Understanding Workshop (COCO Captioning Challenge) at CVPR 2015 Member of Common Visual Data Foundation (CVDF), 2016 - Present Reviewer for CVPR, ICCV, ECCV, NeurIPS and ICML  Selected Honors  McMullen Fellowship (Sep 2014) Edwin Howard Armstrong Memorial Award (May 2014) Wei Family Private Foundation Special Scholarship (Oct 2013) National Scholarship (Oct 2010)  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>